Mss.Ms.Coll.56
American Philosophical Society
- I. Correspondence, Bulk, 1986-2006; 1967-2006; 5.0 Linear feet 13 boxes; Leopold, Luna B. (Luna Bergère), 1915-2006
  - 1. Correspondence Identified by Full Names, 1967-2006; 4.5 ln. ft. 11 boxes
    - Hudson, Hugh H., 1988 (Box 5)
    - Huebner, Betty (Mrs. John M. Heubner) (Box 5)
    - Hunt, Allen S., and Stewart, Dion C., 1978 (Box 5)
    - Hunt, Sarah, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Huppman, L. Reed, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Hustedde, Heddy N. R., 1996 (Box 5)
    - Hynes, Andrew, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Ichim, Ioniţă, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Idaho. Department of Environmental Quality, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Inbar, Meshe, 1980, 1985, 2004 (Box 5)
    - Institute for Environment and Natural Resource Research and Policy, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Institute for Environmental Studies, Instructional Program, 1980 (Box 5)
    - Institute for Sustainable Development, 1996, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Institute on Man and Science, 1980; undated (Box 5)
    - International Conference on Guidelines for Natural Channel Systems, 1st, 1994 (Box 5)
    - International Crane Foundation, 2000 (Box 5)
    - "International Journal of Wilderness", 2001 (Box 5)
    - International Mountain Watershed Symposium Committee, 1990 (Box 5)
    - International Rivers Network, 1996, 2005; undated (Box 5)
    - International Symposium on Erosion and Sediment Transport Measurement (Florence, June 1981), 1980 (Box 5)
    - Irwin, Charles E., 1982 (Box 5)
    - "Isis", 2000 (Box 5)
    - Island Press, 1998 (Box 5)
    - Jackson Hole Allilance for Responsible Planning, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Jackson Hole Historical Center and Museum, 1988 (Box 5)
    - "Jackson Hole News", 2002 (Box 5)
    - Jackson, Roscoe G., II, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Janik, Vincent M., 2000 (Box 5)
    - Jaworski, Cheryl, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Johansen, Finn Roger, 1990 (Box 5)
    - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1999 (Box 5)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1980 (Box 5)
    - John Wiley and Sons Ltd., 2000 (Box 5)
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Johnson, Huey D., circa January 1984 (Box 5)
    - Johnson, R. Roy, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Jones, Eloisa Brown, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Jorgensen, Carl, 1982 (Box 5)
    - "Journal of Hydrology", 2005 (Box 5)
    - Kanivetsky, Roman, 2006 (Box 5)
    - Karp, Frances R. (Mrs. Howard Karp), 1993 (Box 5)
    - Karr, James R., 1993 (Box 5)
      Includes correspondence: Karr, James R. and Leopold, Luna B. to Clinton, William Jefferson (U.S. President).
    - Kattelmann, Richard, 1994, 2000 (Box 5)
    - Katzel, Mitchell, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Kaufman, Sharon, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Kazanski, Christopher, 2000; undated (Box 5)
      This is correspondence from Luna Leopold's young grandson.
    - Kazanski, Clare, 2002, 2005; undated (Box 5)
    - Kazanski, Claude, 1985, 2000-2005 (Box 5)
    - Keller, Ed, circa 1998 (Box 5)
    - Kelly, Tom, 1988, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Kenney, Bergere A., 1977, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Kenney, John J., 1981 (Box 5)
    - Keurs, Dorothy and John, 1988 (Box 5)
    - Kinney, John E., 1985 (Box 5)
    - Kisin, Vitaly, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Knight, Richard L., 1998 (Box 5)
    - Knox, James C., 1999, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Kohler, Kirby, undated (Box 5)
    - Kojan, Gene, 1976 May (Box 5)
      "Conversation with Gene Kojan May 1976" (notes by Luna Leopold).
    - Komar, Paul D., 1989 (Box 5)
    - Korb, Jim, 2001 (Box 5)
    - Koziol, Leslie, undated (Box 5)
    - Lafler, Laura, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Lage, Ann, 1992 (Box 5)
    - LaMoreaux, Philip E., 2005 (Box 5)
    - Landres, Peter, 1997 (Box 5)
    - Landstrom, Karl, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Lange, Becky, 1990 (Box 5)
      Includes correspondence: Lange, Becky to Nicholls, James, 1990.
    - Larabee, Linda, undated (Box 5)
    - Le Fever and Sons, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Ledin, Barb (Mrs. John Ledin), 1985 (Box 5)
    - Leng, Jane and Bob, 2004 (Box 5)
    - Lennette, David A., 1996 (Box 5)
    - Leopold, A. Carl, 1978-2005; undated (Box 6)
    - Leopold, A. Starker, 1980-1981 (Box 6)
    - Leopold, Barbara (Mrs. Luna B. Leopold), 1983, 1998; undated (Box 6)
    - Leopold, Bruce C., 1980-1987; undated (Box 6)
      See also: Oversize Box 1, Folder 0 [zero].
    - Leopold Center for Sustainable Agriculture, 1988, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Leopold Education Project, 1998 (Box 6)
    - Leopold, Estella B., 1978-2005; undated (Box 6)
      Includes items of correspondence of Wright, Vim (Wright, Violet Crane).
    - Leopold, Frederic, 1978-1988; undated (Box 6)
    - Leopold, Kayce Ridgeway, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Leopold, Lynn (Mrs. A. Carl Leopold), undated (Box 6)
    - Leopold, Madelyn (Mrs. Claude Kazanski), 1979, 1985, 2000-2005; undated (Box 6)
      Includes correspondence of Kazanski, Claude.
    - Leverhulme Trust (The), 2005 (Box 6)
    - Levin, Sheldon M., 2005 (Box 6)
    - Liberty and Co. Ltd., 1980 (Box 6)
    - López-Bermúdez, Francsico, 1989, 1997 (Box 6)
    - López-Calle [Family], 2003 (Box 6)
      Includes photo (laser print on paper).
    - Lowham, Hugh W., 1985 (Box 6)
    - Lucchitta, Ivo and Barbel, 1998-2002 (Box 6)
    - Mackay, Ross, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Maddock, Thomas, Jr., 1987 (Box 6)
    - Mah, Bertwing C., 1985 (Box 6)
    - Maher, Leah M., 1985 (Box 6)
    - Marshall, W. Robert, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Marshall, Winifred, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Marston, Richard A., 1998 (Box 6)
    - Martino, Victor, 1994 (Box 6)
    - Marzolf, G. Richard, 1990, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Martinez Regional Land Trust, 1992 (Box 6)
    - May Gallery (The), 1984; undated (Box 6)
      Includes photos of works of art.
    - McBain, Scott, 2002-2004 (Box 6)
      Includes photos (laser prints on paper).
    - McBride, Joe R., 1985, 2004 (Box 6)
    - McCabe, Robert A., 1980, 1985-1987 (Box 6)
    - McClelland, Pam, 2000 (Box 6)
    - McCormick, Katherine, 1989 (Box 6)
    - McGinty, Ken, 2003 (Box 6)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1978, 1999 (Box 6)
    - McHarg, Ian, 1987 (Box 6)
    - McKee, Rusty C. (McKee, Joe), undated (Box 6)
    - McKnighty, Diane, 1994 (Box 6)
    - McKusick, Vincent L., 2003 (Box 6)
    - McLaughlin, Sylvia C., 1994, 2000-2004; undated (Box 6)
    - McPhee, John, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Medellin, Margaret, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Metcalf-Gardipé, Carol M., 2002, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Meunier, Ami/Amy, 1989; undated (Box 6)
    - Miller, Andrew J., 1994 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Bradley, undated (Box 6)
    - Miller, David H., 1988 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Laura C., 1975, 1976, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Mimouni, Omar, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Minnis, Mark Gordon and Mary Beth (Allen), 1984 (Box 6)
    - Mitsubishi International Corporation, 1996 (Box 6)
      Correspondence from Motohiko Numaguchi, President, in response to Leopold comments [no copy here] on proposed San Ignacio Sal facility, Mexico.
    - Montague, Megan, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Montgomery, Roger, undated (Box 6)
    - Movshovitz-Hader, Nitsa, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Mudge, Shaw, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Muir, Mark P., undated (Box 6)
    - Mulvey, Trish, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Museum of the Mountain Man, 2000 (Box 6)
    - Myers, Judi A., 1988 (Box 6)
    - Nagle, Muriel T., 1980 (Box 7)
    - Nakiiende, Florence, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Napa County Resource Conservation District (California), 2000 (Box 7)
    - Nash, Roderick, 1981-1983; undated (Box 7)
    - National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.), 1980 (Box 7)
    - National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.) Proceedings Office., 1980 (Box 7)
    - National Audubon Society, 1994 (Box 7)
    - National Council for Science and the Environment, 2005 (Box 7)
    - National League of American Pen Women, Napa Valley Branch, 1986 (Box 7)
    - National Research Council. (U.S.), 2000 (Box 7)
    - Natural Heritage Institute, 1992, 2002, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2005 (Box 7)
    - Nature Conservancy (The), 1980 (Box 7)
    - Navionics, Inc., 2004 (Box 7)
    - Necessary, Ruth B., 1988 (Box 7)
    - Nelson, Alan R., 1999, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Nelson, Carolyn T., 1984-2004; undated (Box 7)
      Includes correspondence from Anne Ross. See also: Ross, Anne.
    - Nelson, T. Leverett (Nelson, Rett), 1984-2005; undated (Box 7)
    - New Mexico Tech. Department of Geoscience, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Noble, Annette, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Noble Construction, Inc. (Cora, Wyoming), 1998 (Box 7)
    - Noble, James, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Nolan, Thomas B., 1984-1986 (Box 7)
      Incluedes photos.
    - Nolan, Thomas B., family of, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Northern Plains Resource Council, 2005 (Box 7)
    - Northeastern Science Foundation (Rensselaer Center of Applied Geology), 2000 (Box 7)
    - Northern Ireland Council for the Curriculum Examinations and Assessment, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Northland College, 1996-2000 (Box 7)
    - Northeastern Watershed Institute, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Noyes, Daniel, 2005 (Box 7)
    - Oakes, John B., 1999 (Box 7)
    - Oakland Museum/Museum of California Foundation, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Oakwood Village Apartments (Madison, Wisconsin), 1998 (Box 7)
    - O'Brien, Mary, 2000 (Box 7)
    - O'Bryan, Mary, 1979, 1986 (Box 7)
    - O'Connor, Matt, undated (Box 7)
    - Odem, W. L., 1999 (Box 7)
    - Ohio State University. Department of Geology and Mineralogy, 1985 (Box 7)
    - O'Leary, Laura, 2004-2005 (Box 7)
    - O*NET Data Collection Program (RTI International), 2004 (Box 7)
    - Olson, W. Kent, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Oregon Rivers Council, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Osterkamp, Waite, 1990, 1994 (Box 7)
      Includes correspondence: Emmett, William.
    - Otero San Vincente, Napoléon, 1979-1980; undated (Box 7)
    - Oxford University Press, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Oyler, Lynne Dee, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Oyler, Naomi Lynne, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Pacheco-Ceballos, Raul, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Pacific Institute for Studies in Development, Environment, and Security, 1998, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Pacific Rivers Council, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
    - Palmer, Tim, undated (Box 7)
    - Palmes, John, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
    - Pappas, Steve, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Patridge, Ernest, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Patrick, Ruth, 1978-1982, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Patry, Jeff, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
    - Patterson, Elizabeth R., 1994 (Box 7)
    - Peace Garden Project (The), 1986 (Box 7)
    - Pelikan, Jaroslav, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Peñasquítos, Inc., 1978 (Box 7)
    - Perry, Ken, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Perry, James A., 1980 (Box 7)
      Includes "Summary of Conversations with Luna Leopold, Bill Emmett, and the USGS Staff", 2 p.
    - Perry Barlow, John, 1982-1989 (Box 7)
      See also Wyoming Outdoor Council.
    - Peters, Gerald P., 1977 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Katie, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Peters, Rita, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Phibbs, Henry C., II (Phibbs & Resor, P.C.), 1987-1988 (Box 7)
    - Philip, Prince, Duke of Edinburgh, 1987 (Box 7)
      Correspondence from Brigadier Clive Robertson, on behalf of the Duke of Edinburgh.
    - Phillips, Lucie G. C., 1998 (Box 7)
    - Pinedale (Wyoming). Police Department, 1981 (Box 7)
      See also Tubbs, Roy L.
    - Pingree, Isabelle, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Poore, Rick, 1994, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Poppoff, Leo, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Potter, Paul, undated (Box 8)
    - Potter, Van Rensselaer, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
    - Powder River Basin Resource Council (Wyoming), 1978 (Box 8)
    - Prestergaard, Karen, 1978-1989 (Box 8)
    - Priest, George R., 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    - Princeton University Press, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Proudfoot, Bruce and Edwina, undated (Box 8)
    - Quinn, Mary-Louise, 1978-1979, 2000, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Ranney, Sally A., 1981, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Rasmussen, Susan, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Rastetter, William, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Rawlins, Chip L., 1993-2005; undated (Box 8)
    - Reed, Nathaniel Pryor, 1978; undated (Box 8)
    - "Regulated Rivers", 1986 (Box 8)
    - Reiche, Parry, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Reid, Jan, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Reitan, Paul H., 2003 (Box 8)
    - Reynolds, Barbara, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Rhodes, Frank H. T., 2000 (Box 8)
    - Rich, Charles C., 1990 (Box 8)
    - Richards, Mark, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Riddle, Susan, undated (Box 8)
    - Riley, Ann L., 1984-1998 (Box 8)
    - Riparian Habitat Joint Venture (California), 2002 (Box 8)
    - Rival, Mimi, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Rogers, J. David, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Rohwer, Sievert, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Romo, Pam; and the Task Force for Tice Creek (California), undated (Box 8)
    - Rosenshein, Joseph S., 1990 (Box 8)
    - Rosgen, David L., 1993, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Rosgen, Stacey L., 1986 (Box 8)
    - Ross, Anne, 1981; 2002 (Box 8)
      See also Nelson, Carolyn T.
    - Ross, John E., 1980; 1994 (Box 8)
    - Ross, Sally, 1986; undated (Box 8)
    - Rowlands, Kirk O., 2000 (Box 8)
    - Royal Society (The), 1997 (Box 8)
    - Rozengurt, Michael A., 1988 (Box 8)
    - Rush, Elizabeth, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Rushing-Hart, Susan, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Russo, Natalino, undated (Box 8)
    - Ryan, Barbara J., 1999 (Box 8)
    - Sacramento River Watershed Program, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Saint-Onge, Denis A., 1986, 1991, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Salwasser, Hal, 1986 (Box 8)
    - San Francisco Estuary Institute, 1998, 2000 (Box 8)
    - San Francisco Estuary Project, 1998 (Box 8)
    - San Francisco Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    - San Francisco Symphony, undated (Box 8)
    - Sand County Foundation (Wisconsin), 1989, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
    - Sander, Jon, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Saripova, Rahiema, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Schick, Asher P. and Tamar, 1976-1988, 1994, 2002; undated (Box 8)
      Includes correspondence from "Moshe".
    - Schick, Tamar, undated (Box 8)
    - Schmidt, Jack (Schmidt, John C.), 1993 (Box 8)
    - Schmidt, Larry J., 1992 (Box 8)
    - Schneider, Floyd, undated (Box 8)
    - Schulz, Charles G., 1999 (Box 8)
    - Schulz, Ed, 1997, 2003 (Box 8)
    - Schuster, Bob (Schuster, Robert P.) (Box 8)
    - "Science", 1978 (Box 8)
    - Scott, [undetermined], 1985 (Box 8)
    - Sears, Judith, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Sellyei, Joseph, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Sharp, Robert P., 1992-2000 (Box 8)
    - Shields, John W., 2000 (Box 8)
    - Schifflett, Howard, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Shirley, Virginia, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Shontz, Luree, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Shreve, Ron, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Shumway, Cathy, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Shute, Sharie, 1999, 2004 (Box 8)
    - "Sierra", 1987 (Box 9)
    - Sierra Club, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Siever, Raymond, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Simon, Andrew, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Simon Fraser University (British Columbia). Department of Geography, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Simons, Daryl B., 1980 (Box 9)
    - Simpson, Eugene S., 1986 (Box 9)
    - Sinsheimer, Robert L., 1980 (Box 9)
    - Skau, Clarence M., 1980 (Box 9)
    - Skewes-Cox, Bennet, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Skibitzke, Herbert E., 1988 (Box 9)
    - Smith, Caryl, 1999-2004 (Box 9)
    - Smith, Charles E., 1995-1996; undated (Box 9)
    - Smith, Leonard, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Smith, Philip M., 1990 (Box 9)
    - Smith, Richard A., 1994 (Box 9)
    - Smith, Wes, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Snake River Institute (Wyoming), 1997 (Box 9)
    - Sociedad Española de Geomorfología, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Soderstrom, Elizabeth, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Sonnenfeld, Peter, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Sopper, William E., 1970 (Box 9)
    - South Florida Water Management District, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Sowers, Janet M., 2000 (Box 9)
    - Stark, Denise, undated (Box 9)
    - Steinblums, Ivars, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Stent, Peter D., 1993-2000 (Box 9)
      Includes correspondence: Poore, Rick.
    - Steiner, Warren E., Jr., 2004 (Box 9)
    - Stevenson, Hanna A., 1994 (Box 9)
    - Stevenson, Trish and Hanna, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Stewart, Zach R., 1976 (Box 9)
    - Stillwell, Becky, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Stokes, Allen W. and Alice, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Stone, Bethia, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Strong, Ann L., 1976-2005; undated (Box 9)
    - Strom, Margaret A., 1986 (Box 9)
    - Stumm, Werner, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Sublette County (Wyoming). Office of County Treasurer (Box 9)
    - Sublette County (Wyoming) Historical Society, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Sublette County (Wyoming) Library, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Suttle, K. Blake, 2003 (Box 9)
    - Swanson, Mitch; and Goldman, Steve, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Tacconi, Paolo, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Takayama, Shigemi, 1980, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Tam, David, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Taylor, Mary, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Teeguarden, Dennis E., 1996 (Box 9)
    - Teeguarden, Justin, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Tegeler and Associates Insurance, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Templeton, Loie Main, 2005 (Box 9)
    - Terlinden, Dean W., 1994, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Terwilliger, Herbert, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Teton Science School, 1979-2004; undated (Box 9)
    - Thompson, Mike, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Thorne, Colin, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Thornes, John, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Thousand Acre Swamp Sanctuary (Penfield, New York), 1981 (Box 9)
    - Tourtelot, Harry A., 1988 (Box 9)
    - Trainer, F. W., 1978 (Box 9)
    - Trimble, Stanley W., 1986 (Box 9)
    - Tropical Forestry Initiative, 1993, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Trout Unlimited, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Trovato, Ben, 1997-2003; undated (Box 9)
      Pseudonym of Claudio Vita-Finzi. Leopold received correspondence from this individual as both "Claudio" and as "Ben Trovato" or "B.T." See also Vita-Finzi, Claudio.
    - Trush, Sheri, 2002 (Box 9)
    - Trust for Public Land (California), 1998 (Box 9)
    - Tseo, George, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Tubbs, Roy L., 1980 (Box 9)
      See also Pinedale (Wyoming). Police Department.
    - Turk, John T., 2002 (Box 9)
    - Twidale, C. Rowland, 2005 (Box 9)
    - Twiss, Robert H., 1986 (Box 9)
    - Ulibarri, Ling, undated (Box 10)
    - United Nations, 1978 (Box 10)
    - United States. Congress. Office of Technology Assessment, undated (Box 10)
    - United States. Customs Service, 1980 (Box 10)
    - United States. Fish and Wildlife Service. Bird Banding Section, 1993 (Box 10)
    - United States. Forest Service. Bridger-Teton National Forest, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - United States. Forest Service. Pinedale Ranger District, 1980 (Box 10)
    - United States. Forest Service. Washington Office, 1989, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
    - United States. Geological Survey. Library, 2004 (Box 10)
    - Universidad de Murcia, 1988 (Box 10)
    - University of Arizona Press, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
    - University of California. Water Resources Center, 1980 (Box 10)
    - University of California at Berkeley. College of Environmental Design, 1989 (Box 10)
    - University of California at Berkeley. Committee on Research, 1979-1980 (Box 10)
    - University of California at Berkeley. Department of Geology and Geophysics, 1989 (Box 10)
    - University of California at Berkeley. Department of Landscape Architecture, 1978-1988 (Box 10)
    - University of California at Berkeley. Natural Resources Library, 1987 (Box 10)
    - University of California at Berkeley. Water Resources Center Archives, 1997, 2004 (Box 10)
    - University of California at Santa Barbara. Environmental Studies Program, 1986 (Box 10)
    - University of California Press, 1993 (Box 10)
    - University of Cincinnati. Department of Geology, 1985 (Box 10)
    - University of Colorado at Boulder. Department of Civil, Environmental, and Architectural Engineering, 1999 (Box 10)
    - University of Haifa (Israel). Office of the Rector, 1998 (Box 10)
    - University of New England (Australia), 1980 (Box 10)
    - University of New Mexico. Department of Geology, 1988 (Box 10)
    - University of New Mexico. Utton Transboundary Resources Center, 2002 (Box 10)
    - University of Newcastle upon Tyne. Registrar's Office, 1993 (Box 10)
    - University of Pittsburgh. School of Engineering, 1986 (Box 10)
    - University of St. Andrews American Foundation, Inc., 1987 (Box 10)
    - University of Washington. College of Arts and Sciences. Dean's Club, 2005 (Box 10)
    - University of Washington. Office of the President (Box 10)
    - University of Washington. President's Club, 2004 (Box 10)
    - University of Wisconsin at Madison. College of Engineering, 1988 (Box 10)
    - University of Wisconsin at Madison. Department of Geography, 1992 (Box 10)
    - University of Wisconsin at Madison. University News Service, 1980 (Box 10)
    - University of Wisconsin Foundation, 2004-2005 (Box 10)
    - University of Wisconsin Press, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Urban Creeks Council, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Vahey, Magnolia, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Van Hagan, Charles, 1993-1994 (Box 10)
    - Vierbicher Associates, undated (Box 10)
    - Vincent, Kirk R., 1980, 1993-1994, 2000; undated (Box 10)
    - Vita-Finzi, Claudio, 1989-2004; undated (Box 10)
      Leopold received correspondence from this individual as both "Claudio" and as the pseudonym "Ben Trovato" or "B.T." See also Trovato, Ben.
    - Vita-Finzi, Penelope, 2000, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Vleck, David, 2005 (Box 10)
    - W. H. Freeman and Co., 1978, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Wagner, Frederic H., 1993 (Box 10)
    - Waite, John, 1992; undated (Box 10)
    - Walling, D. E., 1986 (Box 10)
    - Walter, Christopher C., 1980 (Box 10)
    - Wan, Ray, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Washington. Department of Energy, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Washington Environmental Council, 2003 (Box 10)
    - "Water Resources Research", 1986 (Box 10)
    - Watershed Management Council, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Waterways Restoration Institute, 1998; undated (Box 10)
    - Wegner, Steve, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Weisheit, John, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Wendorf, Fred, 1987, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Werritty, Alan, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Western Environmental Law Center, 2005 (Box 10)
    - White, Dale, 1986 (Box 10)
    - White, Gilbert F., 1990-2005 (Box 10)
    - White, Marshall, 1994, 2000 (Box 10)
    - Whole Earth Jamboree 1978 (Box 10)
    - Wiggs, Giles F. S., 1998 (Box 10)
    - Wilcock, Peter R., 2005 (Box 10)
    - Wilcox, Marc, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Wilderness Science Conference, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Wilderness Society (The), 1983, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Wilderness Watch, 1999-2004 (Box 11)
    - Williamson, Dolores, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Wills-Forani, Ludmilla, 1975-1978; undated (Box 11)
    - Wilson, Douglas L., 1985 (Box 11)
    - Wilson, Richard A., 1993 (Box 11)
    - Winkley, Brien R., 1980 (Box 11)
    - Wisconsin Academy of Sciences, Arts and Letters, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Woldenberg, Mike, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Wolf, Peter O., 1993 (Box 11)
    - Wolman, M. Gordon (Wolman, Reds), 1984-2004 (Box 11)
    - Woodruff, Charles, Jr., 1989 (Box 11)
    - Wood's Photo Supplies (Hong Kong), 1977 (Box 10)
    - Woodward-Clyde International-Americas, 1998 (Box 11)
    - World Innovation Foundation, 2000 (Box 11)
    - "WRD Retirees" (Water Resources Division, U.S. Geological Survey), 1990 (Box 11)
    - Wright, Violet Crane (Wright, Vim), 1997-2001 (Box 11)
      See also Leopold, Estella.
    - Wyoming Outdoor Council, 1982-1998 (Box 11)
      See also Perry Barlow, John.
    - Wyoming Telephone Co., Inc., 1978 (Box 11)
    - Wyoming Wildlife Federation, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Yake, Hank, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Yang, C. T., 1986 (Box 11)
    - Yochelson, Ellis L., 1978-1980 (Box 11)
    - Zabawa, Christopher F., 1998 (Box 11)
    - Zamarripa, Dina Marie, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Zeff, Marjorie L., 2003 (Box 11)
    - Zen, E-an, 1978-1988; undated (Box 11)
    - Zinc, M. D., 2001 (Box 11)
    - Zullo, Victor A., 1985 (Box 11)
  - 2. Correspondence Identified Only by Familiar Names and Undetermined, 0.5 ln. ft. 2 boxes
    Subseries 2 contains correspondence from individuals known only by given names, along with correspondence whose signers have not been deciphered, and unsigned correspondence.
    - Allen and Alice, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Anita, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Audrey and Bart, 1994, 1998, 2004 (Box 12)
    - Barbara Jean, 2003 (Box 12)
    - Barry, undated (Box 12)
    - Becky, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Beth, 1999, 2001 (Box 12)
    - Betsey, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Betty (1), 1984 (Box 12)
    - Betty (2) and Jim, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Bill (1), undated (Box 12)
    - Bill (2), 1986 (Box 12)
    - Bill (3), 1986 (Box 12)
    - Bill K., 2005 (Box 12)
    - BJ, undated (Box 12)
    - Bob (1), 1989 (Box 12)
    - Bob (2) and Amy, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - Burt, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
    - Burt and Ava, 2000, 2004 (Box 12)